AHMED NABIL MAJEED

Human.ahmed87@gmail.com +964 750 830 4340

I believe that my strong educational background and extensive experience in the field, make an appropriate candidate for the advertised position. As you can see in the enclosed resume, I have been working is sites and field for years. Since, my responsibilities and duties were quite similar to those required in the ad of your organization; I strongly believe I can perform well all the delegated duties and tasks.

PERSONAL INFO:

Nationality: Iraq Gender: Male Date of Birth: 1987

OBJECTIVE:

To secure a position in a challenging environment, looking forward to make result-oriented contributions towards completion of projects with extensive knowledge and rich experience aiding in constantly monitoring the progress of projects Seeking.

EDUCATION:

Private University of Science and Art, Aleppo, Syria.

B.Sc. in Architecture Engineering: July 2012

SKILLS

Architectural & Computer: Strong organizational skills, Proper site management methods, Proficient in Autodesk AutoCAD 2018, Adobe Photoshop CS5; Microsoft Office 2019. Moderate usage of 3DS Max 2017.

NGO's Skills: High communication abilities, Well Knowledge in data collecting & analysis, absolutely familiar with kobo data collection program, ODK Collect program, survey CTO Collect, expert in the distribution process from site choosing, organization to the PDM, Well Knowledge in logistic and finance process in all project stages.

Certification:

Basic & Advance Security in the field / CALP / Stress management NGO's Policies / First Aid Training Languages:

Arabic mother tongue. English (Very good). Kurdish (Moderate)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

Nasswallet Co. /Iraq, April 2021- Present

Position: Nasswallet / Cooperate Sale Executive

Project Description: Responsible for all Nasswallet merchants' activities in Erbil.

Follow up the performance of the Merchants.

Identify and sign new Merchants.

Train the Merchants for the Program and make sure the Merchants is updated with all new Information.

Zain Co. /Iraq, August 2020 - April 2021

Position: Zain Cash / Erbil Account Manager

Project Description: Responsible for all Zain Cash activities in Erbil.

Follow up the performance of the delegates.

Identify and sign new POS's

Follow up registration process

Keep tracking the POS transactions and their awareness.

Train the Dealer for the new offers and make sure the Pos is updated with all new Information.

Monitor Zain Cash Registration Events.

Oxfam. / Roving, Iraq, June 2018 - Nov 2019 Project: SIDA / collect, Analysis data/ Distribution Place:

Mosul.

Project Description: collect & analysis data and Distribution for about 1800 HH.

Project: OFDA / collect, Analysis data/ Distribution

Place: Salahuddin/Baiji.

Project Description: collect & analysis data and Distribution for about 1500 HH.

Norwegian Refugee Consul. / Erbil, Iraq, February 2016 – 2017 Project: GIZ collect & Analysis data

Position: Rapid Response Assistant.

Project Description: collect & analysis data for about 3800 IDPs & Refugees.

Project: GIZ Market Assessment.

Position: Rapid Response Assistant.

Project Description: assessment & Price Monitoring for about 15 Market.

Project: Shelter Department Cash Distribution.

Position: Volunteer.

Project Description: Cash distribution for about 400 IDPs & Refugees.

Nippur Construction solutions. / Erbil, Iraq, October 2014 – 2015

Project: Sprint offices Project & Lab Position: Designer & Supervising

Project Description: Sandwich Panel 2 level offices & Container Convert to Be Lab Project: NLS Oil Field

Tanks

Position: Designer & Supervising

Project Description: 90m3 Oil Field High Pressure Tanks

Rasan Contracting Co. / Erbil, Iraq, September 2012 – 2014

Project: Fruits and Vegetables Sales Center Project Time: September 2012 – 2013

Position: Site Inspector

Project Description: shopping complex with 5 sale halls and 200 retail units and other back of house

facilities (storages, cooled storages, parking...etc.)

Project: Mamustayan Residential Project Time: September 2013 – September 2014

Position: Concept Design Architect (master planning and architectural design) Project Description:

Almost 1,900 town house villas and apartments.

Other projects:

MOL KALEGRAN: site inspector/ finishes. 2013.